<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Curse of Strahd]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/</link><image><url>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Curse of Strahd</title><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:15:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:14:52 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></copyright><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator>TheOnlyKay</dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[The Flaming Skull]]></title><description><![CDATA[
Tavern located in <a data-href="Olostin's Hold" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/locations/forgotten-realms/olostin's-hold/olostin's-hold.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Olostin's Hold</a>
Named after The Flaming Skull floating in the center of the Tavern
]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/locations/forgotten-realms/olostin&apos;s-hold/the-flaming-skull-tavern/the-flaming-skull.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Forgotten Realms/Olostin&apos;s Hold/The Flaming Skull Tavern/The Flaming Skull.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<a data-href="#Session 0 - 06-02-2025" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/#Session_0_-_06-02-2025_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Session 0 - 06-02-2025</a>
<br><a data-href="#Session 0.5 - 15-02-2025" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/#Session_0.5_-_15-02-2025_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Session 0.5 - 15-02-2025</a>
<br><a data-href="#Session 1 - 25-02-2025" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/#Session_1_-_25-02-2025_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Session 1 - 25-02-2025</a>
<br><a data-href="#Session 2 - 11-03-2025" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/#Session_2_-_11-03-2025_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Session 2 - 11-03-2025</a>
We decided to roll for ability stats, everyone rolls 4d6 drop lowest, with this we get 5 rows of 6 values:<br>Campaign we'll be running is called <a data-href="Curse of Strahd" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Curse of Strahd</a>
This is a "scarier" campaign, horror-level at the same level as the Rivermoot arc from Storm King's Thunder.If a topic, or story aspect goes too far, don't be afraid to immediately tell it.We need to decide how we all met and where we are at the start of session 1.
Keanu and Marleen know each other longer, kind of a Sherlock-Watson type duo --&gt; This backstory also needs to be figured out.Forget about Dark Gifts25e Februari bij Kris om 18.00u, zullen ook daar gezamelijk etenNeed to figure out the age of Kaelion when everything happenedKeanu en Marleen bij Keanu thuisCharacter info's
Zelfde Leeftijd
Brother Vibes
Mag een trinket rollen:<br>
<a data-href="Kaelion Sylren" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/kaelion-sylren.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kaelion Sylren</a>'s Trinket: 1-ounce block made from unknown material
Stillere achtergrond types
<br><a data-href="Sariel" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/sariel/sariel.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Sariel</a> is opgegroeid in SIlverymoon
Platonic Soulmates Leren kenner
Hookup 1/2 times
Verder als vrienden
Wel flirty 0-750 totaal elven leven
Min. 100 jaar samen
rond 80-100 weg
ong. 10 jaar alleen
James 3-4 jaar alleen --&gt; roudyKaelion:
92 --&gt; weg
2 weken erna ontmoeting met James waar we niet over praten (wink, wink)
Elkaar uit oog verloren
96 --&gt; James weer tegengekomen besloten samen verder te reizen
ongeveer 214 als we aan de campaign beginnen
My type in boys:
Hook-ups, no relationships
NO ELVES
Tieflings are preference
Bad Boys
Taller than me
Player overzicht:<br>We start our adventure in a tavern, <a data-href="The Flaming Skull" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/locations/forgotten-realms/olostin's-hold/the-flaming-skull-tavern/the-flaming-skull.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Flaming Skull</a> in <a data-href="Olostin's Hold" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/locations/forgotten-realms/olostin's-hold/olostin's-hold.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Olostin's Hold</a>, a tavern named for the flaming skull in the middle of the tavern.
It's a busy tavern, where Kaelion, Sariel, Buttercup and Arnihl all share a table, they've known each other for a few months now, travelling on the roads together.
With it being a busy night, strangers are bound to be sat together, as is the deal with Sabor, an Aasimar, who joins our table. A table full of well-traveled people that now looks a lot like a group of adventurers.<br>As a bartender takes our order she looks around the table and sees us - A party of adventurers (<a data-href="Party" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/party.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Party</a>):
Arnihl: A 2.2m tall Goliath with gray skin, no hair and completely black eyes drinking his problems away - hails from the Spine of the world
Buttercup: A 1.2m tall gnome, dressed in leaf-like clothes, all earthly color, with a long braid of dark brown hair
Sabor: An Aasimar with blue metallic skin, black spiky hair, dressed in black/red leathers. Kind of like a tiefling without horns, but with a tail - hails from Triboar
Sariel: A High Elf dressed in green colours, long green hair bound in a ponytail
Kaelion: A Wood Elf dressed quite nicely with long red hair braided on the side of their head, but in a loose ponytail
We decide to get some rooms for the night, and ask the barmaid what the price of that would be. A simple room costs 5sp per room per night.<br>
The barmaid also mentions that <a data-href="The Lady of the Hold" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/npc's/the-lady-of-the-hold.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Lady of the Hold</a> would have work for adventurers, and if we're interested we should talk to herWe share a conversation about who we are and what we do, Arnihl likes to punch people with his fists, Sariel and Kaelion keep mysterious by saying they "dabble", Sabor makes a sword magically appear, with a green flash and smoke that smells a lot like an old, ancient forest. Buttercup is good at shooting people and generally sneaking around.
Buttercup, out of nowhere, asks everyone if they have scars, Arnihl mentions he has too many to count, Sabor says he's too prett to have scars, Sariel has some scratches here and there, the unavoidable ones. Kaelion mentions he has a large scar across his back that they might someday show to Buttercup.<br>In the middle of this conversation, a female human walks in, broad shoulders, long black curly hair. She almost walks past our table, but doubles back and introduces herself as Tamalin, <a data-href="The Lady of the Hold" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/npc's/the-lady-of-the-hold.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Lady of the Hold</a>. There's trouble around the hold, now that the giant issues appear to be solved. There are werewolves plaguing the hold and the surrounding area. There are men-wolf shapeshifters causing trouble roughly 5-6 miles west of <a data-href="Olostin's Hold" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/locations/forgotten-realms/olostin's-hold/olostin's-hold.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Olostin's Hold</a>. If we manage to clear out the issue and bring her proof of this (preferably in the form of heads) we will be awarded 100gp for the group. The attacks happen mostly at midnight, and are not bound to the stance of the moon. The only other piece of advice Tamalin gives us is; Don't get bitten by the werewolves.After a long rest in the tavern we get to the hall where Tamalin has kindly given us backpacks with basic supplies; bedroll, torches, rations, and the likes.<br>After a hearty breakfast we head on out, by foot, to the west. Roughly 5-6 miles away from <a data-href="Olostin's Hold" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/locations/forgotten-realms/olostin's-hold/olostin's-hold.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Olostin's Hold</a> we stumble upon a deserted wagon, covered in claw marks, no bodies around. appears to be a group of 5-6 people.Thankfully the attackers (most likely the werewolves) left tracks that Kaelion manages to follow into the woods.
Marching order walking through the woods: Kaelion - Arnihl - Buttercup - Sariel - Sabor--- Early end because Mirko does not feel good ---]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Buttercup Stumpington]]></title><description><![CDATA[Buttercup Stumpington is portrayed by MarianneA 1.2m tall gnome, dressed in leaf-like clothes, all earthly color, with a long braid of dark brown hair]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/buttercup-stumpington/buttercup-stumpington.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Playable Characters/Buttercup Stumpington/Buttercup Stumpington.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kaelion - Level 1]]></title><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/character-sheets/kaelion-level-1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Playable Characters/Kaelion Sylren/Character Sheets/Kaelion - Level 1.pdf</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Older Kaelion]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/pictures/older-kaelion.jpg" target="_self">]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/pictures/older-kaelion.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Playable Characters/Kaelion Sylren/Pictures/Older Kaelion.jpg</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/pictures/older-kaelion.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/pictures/older-kaelion.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Young Kaelion]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/pictures/young-kaelion.jpg" target="_self">]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/pictures/young-kaelion.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Playable Characters/Kaelion Sylren/Pictures/Young Kaelion.jpg</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/pictures/young-kaelion.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/pictures/young-kaelion.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kaelion Sylren]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kealion is portrayed by Keanu
A large scar on their back, seeing it would instantly remind someone of a claw mark Kaelion got this scar while in WildShape protecting themself from a direwolf while living in isolation
This happened in the first year of Kaelion's isolation <a data-href="Kaelion - Level 1.pdf" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/character-sheets/kaelion-level-1.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kaelion - Level 1.pdf</a> <br>Kaelion Sylren was born under a sky of falling stars, a celestial omen that foretold great significance. <a data-href="The Skywatchers of the High Forest" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/locations/forgotten-realms/high-forest/the-skywatchers-of-the-high-forest.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Skywatchers of the High Forest</a>, an ancient tribe of wood elves, believed that the heavens wove the tapestry of fate, and those who could read the stars, could catch glimpses of the future. It was said that those born under extraordinary celestial events were destined for something great- something extraordinary. This meant that Kaelion's destiny was intertwined with the stars themselves, as if Kaelion was written into the very fabric of the cosmos. From a young age they have felt this connection deep in their bones, as though the heavens themselves were speaking directly to Kaelion.<br>Growing up in the heart of the High Forest, a vast and untouched wilderness, Kaelion was drawn to the mysteries of the night sky. As a child, they would often wander from the safety of their family's home, slipping into the cool night air to gaze up at the stars. With every nightfall, they felt the pull of the sky-its patterns, its hidden meanings. Kaelion would trace constellations, carefully sketching the observations into an old, worn journal, convinced that each star held a secret to be discovered. These quiet, solitary moments under the vast canopy of stars were Kaelion's greatest joy, and it was during these nights that they first met <a data-href="Eluna Stormwhisper" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/npc's/eluna-stormwhisper.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Eluna Stormwhisper</a>, a fellow Skywatcher apprentice.Eluna was everything that Kaelion wasn't. Where Kaelion was intuitive, feeling their way through the mysteries of the world, Eluna was meticulous, driven by a thirst for knowledge and a determination to understand the hidden truths of the stars. Unlike the rest of the tribe, who seemed to grasp the celestial arts with natural ease, Eluna had to work tirelessly to connect with the heavens. Yet it was this very dedication that Kaelion admired-Eluna's drive was infectious, and the two quickly became inseparable. They spent their days together, training in the druidic arts, learning how to speak to the land and commune with the natural world. Their nights were spent mapping the heavens, tracing the paths of the stars, searching for meaning in the ever-changing sky.The bond between Kaelion and Eluna grew stronger with each passing season. The two were more than companions; they were partners, friends, and, perhaps unknowingly, two souls bound by the very stars they studied. They often spoke about destiny and adventure, dreaming of the day they would leave the High Forest behind, exploring the world beyond the trees. Eluna, more than anyone, understood Kaelion's deep connection to the celestial world and was always there to challenge their assumptions, push them to learn more, to see beyond the obvious.Eluna was Kaelion's light in the darkness- the one person who knew Kaelion inside and out, who shared their passion for the stars and their dreams of a world full of discovery. Together they were unstoppable, a force that seemed destined for greatness.But as the seasons passed, something ominous began to stir in the heavens. The stars seemed to shift, becoming restless, as if preparing to reveal something the world was not ready to know.One evening, as Kaelion and Eluna gazed up at the sky, a sudden flash of light caught their attention. An unfamiliar constellation flickered into existence, its patterns unlike any Kaelion had seen before. At first, it was faint, a brief flash of light among the familiar stars. But then it pulsed, a steady, rhythmic glow that seemed to pulse with an unspoken energy. Kaelion's heart skipped a beat, there was something deeply wrong with the stars that night, something they couldn't explain, yet it gnawed at Kaelion's very soul.Kaelion turned to Eluna, seeking answers, but the look in their companion's eyes mirrored the same unease Kaelion felt. Eluna was already searching for her quarterstaff, her eyes scanning the trees. She could sense it too. The sense of foreboding was palpable, hanging in the air like a heavy fog.Before Kaelion could speak, they felt it- a sudden and overwhelming sense of loss, as though the very stars were trying to communicate something urgent. They looked around to find Eluna, calling out her name, but Eluna was gone, their usual spot, beneath the ancient oak tree where they had spent countless nights together, was empty. There were no signs, no clues- only an eerie silence. The stars overhead flickered and dimmed, as if to mark her absence.Frantic, Kaelion searched the forest for days, rallying others from the tribe to help. They combed the wilderness, scouring every familiar trail. every nook and cranny where Eluna could have gone. Yet, despite their efforts, there was no sign of Eluna. Days turned to weeks, and still, no trace of her could be found. The tribe began to whisper, their voices filled with suspicion and dread. Some believed Eluna had been taken by dark forces, others thought she had simply wandered too far and perished. But Kaelion knew the truth deep in their heart: the stars had tried to warn them, but they had failed to understand.The very omen that had signaled Eluna's disappearance was a mystery in itself, a cosmic puzzle that Kaelion could not solve. But they were sure of one thing: the stars had not just guided Eluna away- they had chosen her for something, something Kaelion was not meant to know.Kaelion was consumed by guilt and sorrow. They could not bear the thought of continuing their life among the tribe while Eluna's fate remained uncertain. For years, Kaelion isolated themselves from the tribe, retreating into the deep wilds of the High Forest. There, they found solace only in the company of the land and the sky- the whispering winds and the distant stars seemed to call out to them, ever so faintly. They spent their days meditating, their nights tracing constellations in the hopes that one day, they would find the answer to what happened to Eluna.Time passed, but Kaelion's heart remained broken. Memories of Eluna haunted their every step, and every night beneath the stars felt like a reminder of what had been lost. Yet Kaelion couldn't stop searching, even as the world outside the forest moved on.Now, years later, Kaelion's heart has stirred once again. The strange constellation that had flickered into existence the night Eluna vanished has reappeared, brighter and more intense than ever before. Its light pulses with an unspoken message, one Kaelion feels deep within their bones- this is no coincidence. The time has come. The stars are calling again, but this time, Kaelion knows they cannot ignore their summons.The mourning is over, and the stars have not forgotten them. With their quarterstaff in hand, a new resolve has taken root within Kaelion. They must seek the truth, no matter the cost. The search for Eluna is no longer just a matter of grief- it is a quest for understanding, for redemption, and for the cosmic answers that have eluded them for so long.With the wisdom of the heavens as their guide, Kaelion steps beyond the forest's borders, ready to follow the stars wherever they may lead. Whether the path leads to redemption or ruin, Kaelion will no longer hide from the truth. The stars have spoken, and Kaelion will answer.I was 92 when I left the High Forest. I remember the silence that followed me, a shadow that refused to let go. For the first time in my life, the stars above felt distant—cold pinpricks of light against an unforgiving sky. I wandered aimlessly, following no path but the one my feet carved through the earth. Days bled into nights, weeks into months. Half a year of solitude, drifting from one place to another, a nameless ghost with no destination.<br>Then I stumbled into Citadel Fellbar, weary and hungry, longing for a momentary escape from my thoughts. The tavern was loud, chaotic—a cacophony of laughter and drunken shouts. I found a corner to hide in, hoping to disappear among the noise. That’s when I heard his voice. Warm, inviting, reckless. <a data-href="Sariel" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/sariel/sariel.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Sariel</a>.I didn’t mean to laugh at his jokes, but I did. I didn’t mean to drink so much, but the mugs kept coming. By the end of the night, I was tangled in his embrace, his breath warm against my neck, his laughter echoing in my ears. It was the first time in months that I felt alive. But come morning, fear settled in—fear of connection, of attachment, of losing someone again. So I left. I slipped out before dawn, leaving nothing but a cold, empty bed behind.Part of me hoped I’d never see him again. It would be easier that way. But the stars are cruel—they weave fates we cannot escape.I wandered once more, retreating into the wilds, avoiding cities whenever I could. For nearly four years, I lived as a hermit, surrounded by trees and shadows, speaking only to the wind. Loneliness became a companion, a familiar ache I could not cure. Yet even then, I could not forget the way Sariel laughed, the warmth of his smile.Fate, it seems, was not finished with me.I found myself near Luskan, a bustling harbor city brimming with life and noise. I only meant to stop for a meal, a brief respite from the road. The tavern was crowded, the air thick with salt and laughter. I ate quietly, head down, until I heard a voice—familiar, teasing, unforgettable.“Look who it is, the elf that snuck away from me. Kaelion, was it?”I turned, and there he was. Sariel, grinning like he’d won the world. I didn’t know what to say. But he laughed, clapped me on the back, and ordered two mugs of ale before I could protest. We talked for hours, slipping easily into conversation, as if no time had passed at all.We agreed to travel together—just for a few days, we said. But days became weeks, weeks became months, and before I knew it, years had passed. We wandered the Sword Coast, getting into trouble, sharing stories beneath star-filled skies. Somewhere along the way, he became my family—the brother I never had.A decade slipped by unnoticed. I no longer remembered what it felt like to be alone. We became inseparable, two souls tied by fate and laughter, drawn together by the whims of the stars.Over a century has passed since that day in Luskan. Sariel is still by my side, a constant in this ever-changing world. Together, we solve mysteries, chase shadows, laugh in the face of danger. I no longer run from my past—I face it, with him beside me.The stars may be distant, but they have led me to where I need to be. And as long as Sariel is with me, I know I’m not alone.Before I left the High Forest, the magic of the wilds flowed through me as naturally as breath. I could call upon the winds, mend wounds with a whisper, and shift my form to run with the beasts of the land. The stars, ever watchful, guided my path—whispering truths in the quiet of the night.But the night I lost Eluna, I lost my faith as well. The heavens had shown me an omen, a sign I failed to understand. If the stars truly held our fates, then why had they stolen the one person I could not bear to lose?So I turned my back on them.When I vanished into the wilds, I left more than my tribe behind—I left my magic. At first, it was out of defiance. Then, it became habit. The power I once wielded dulled, like an unused blade left to rust. A decade passed, and the wilds became my home, but the magic no longer felt like it was mine. Not using it became my new normal.When I finally returned to the world, I did so as an echo of what I had been. Sariel never questioned it. He knew I could handle myself, but he never saw the magic I once held. He never knew that I had once called upon the sky to answer my will. And I never told him.Even now, I hesitate. The stars have begun to shift again, their whispers creeping back into my thoughts. My magic stirs like an ember buried beneath cold ash. But do I dare rekindle it?
Starry-Eyed Dreamer - Kaelion often loses themselves staring at the night sky, mid-conversation, mid-battle, or even mid-bite. They'll pause, eyes locked on a constellation, muttering, "Strange... that star wasn't there last week"
Symbolic Rituals - Kaelion has a habit of drawing constellations in the dirt or carving them into wood when deep in thought. When nervous, they might trace a star shape on their wrist with their finger.
Cryptic but Playful - They have a way of speaking in vague, mysterious phrases, even when it's unnecessary "The stars whisper of many paths... but sure, let's take the left one"
They sometimes exaggerate their "mystical wisdom" to mess with people, only to wink after. Odd Sleeping Habits - Kaelion sleeps outside whenever possible, even if there's a perfectly good inn, they'd rather be under the stars. Indoors, they position themselves by a windows, restless if they can't see the night sky.
Celestial Cooking - They like to align their meals with the phases of the moon (e.g. only eating certain herbs or brewing specific teas during certain lunar cycles.) Whether or not it actually changes anything... well, they insist it does.
Unshakably Calm... Until they don't have their Quarterstaff -Kaelion is typically serene and wise, but if someone misplaces or damages their quarterstaff (which they hand-carved with star patterns together with Eluna), they get unexpectedly flustered and dramatic.
Sylwen is a Druid and a Skywatcher Elder
A stoic and wise elven woman, deeply respected in the tribe for her celestial readings and connection to the land.
She was a guiding but distant presence in Kaelion's life, expecting them to embrace their role as a druid and protector of the stars.
Kaelion adores her but also resents the pressure she placed on them, feeling as though their destiny was decided before they could choose.
She never fully approved of Kaelion's deep bond with Eluna, believing their friendship was a distraction from their sacred duties.
]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/kaelion-sylren.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Playable Characters/Kaelion Sylren/Kaelion Sylren.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/pictures/young-kaelion.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/pictures/young-kaelion.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sabor]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sabor is portrayed by KrisAn Aasimar with blue metallic skin, black spiky hair, dressed in black/red leathers. Kind of like a tiefling without horns, but with a tail - hails from Triboar]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/sabor/sabor.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Playable Characters/Sabor/Sabor.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sariel]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/sariel/pictures/sariel.jpg" target="_self">]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/sariel/pictures/sariel.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Playable Characters/Sariel/Pictures/Sariel.jpg</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/sariel/pictures/sariel.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/sariel/pictures/sariel.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sariel]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img alt="Sariel.jpg" src="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/sariel/pictures/sariel.jpg" target="_self" style="width: 325px; max-width: 100%;">Sariel is portrayed by MarleenSariel's full name is Sánëisilsaríël, one which Kaelion only uses if Sariel is in trouble<br>
Sariel and <a data-href="Kaelion Sylren" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/kaelion-sylren.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kaelion Sylren</a> have traveled together for over 100 years now"When you have eliminated the impossible, whatever remains, however improbable, must be the truth" Opgegroeid in Silvery Moon als Noble, Naam Sáneisilsarfet betekend noble pine crown moon elf, maar zijn roepnaam is Sariel.
Zijn familile is aanhanger van Temple of the Silver Stars, Selûne followers. Rond mijn 92e weggegaan. Hierna mijn wilde jaren.
Rond 96e Kaelion (weer) ontmoet en samen gaan reizen.
Dik 100 jaar samen gereisd We zijn beiden rond de 214 jaar oud aan het begin van de campaign.
Kaelion = platonic soulmate Karaktertrekjes: Kan absoluut niet met geld omgaan, Kaelion beheert zijn portomonee om deze reden; Heeft mooi handschrift maar kan absoluut niet iets tekenen; Rustig: Soms beetje wereldvreemd (imean WIS is dumpstat) Valt op: Males. Human Sailor/Muscly types. Elves, Drow elegant and mysterious types Alignment: LN]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/sariel/sariel.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Playable Characters/Sariel/Sariel.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/sariel/pictures/sariel.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/sariel/pictures/sariel.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Party]]></title><description><![CDATA[Party members:
<a data-href="Arnihl" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/arnihl/arnihl.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arnihl</a>
<br><a data-href="Buttercup Stumpington" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/buttercup-stumpington/buttercup-stumpington.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Buttercup Stumpington</a>
<br><a data-href="Kaelion Sylren" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/kaelion-sylren/kaelion-sylren.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kaelion Sylren</a>
<br><a data-href="Sabor" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/sabor/sabor.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Sabor</a>
<br><a data-href="Sariel" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/sariel/sariel.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Sariel</a>
]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/party.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Playable Characters/Party.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Skywatchers of the High Forest]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hidden beneath the towering boughs of the High Forest, the Skywatchers are an ancient and reclusive elven order devoted to the study of the stars. They believe the celestial dance of the heavens reflects the rhythms of life on the Material Plane, offering guidance, omens, and glimpses into the great cosmic design. To them, the stars are not merely distant lights but spirits—ancestors, lost gods, and cosmic sentinels watching over the world.The origins of the Skywatchers stretch back thousands of years, to a time when elves first walked the High Forest beneath skies untainted by civilization’s glow. According to their oldest myths, they were once simple wanderers who gazed upon the stars in wonder, until a being of celestial radiance—known only as the Starborne—descended from the heavens. This figure, neither wholly divine nor mortal, is said to have gifted them with the first teachings of the Skyborn Mantle, allowing them to align their spirits with the celestial and natural world alike.From that moment on, the Skywatchers devoted themselves to the study of the cosmos, believing that the stars held not just wisdom, but the echoes of those who came before. The most ancient of their prophecies speak of great celestial events shaping the fate of the world—some foreseen, others still waiting to be unveiled.For centuries, the Skywatchers have remained isolated, only rarely engaging with outsiders. They hold deep mistrust for those who exploit nature or seek to control fate through magic or ambition. However, there are rare times when they send emissaries to intervene in events foretold in their star charts.Legends tell of Skywatchers appearing at critical moments in history—on battlefields, at the births of great heroes, or in times when the balance of the world teeters on a knife’s edge. To those unfamiliar with their ways, they are mysterious and unpredictable, but to those who understand their beliefs, they are simply keepers of an ancient and intricate cosmic dance.The Skywatchers live by the principle that "The heavens are a map, but not a master." While they look to the stars for wisdom, they also acknowledge that mortals have the power to shape their own fate. However, interpretations of this philosophy vary within the order. Some believe in strict adherence to prophecy, while others, like the hunters and wanderers among them, argue that the stars are meant to guide, not dictate.Their rituals are deeply tied to celestial cycles:
The Moonwake Rites honor ancestors beneath a full moon, with songs and spectral visions cast upon the sacred pools.
The Starborne Vigil is a solitary journey undertaken by initiates, where they must spend a night under the open sky, seeking their first personal revelation from the cosmos.
The Passing of the Mantle is the most sacred of rites, marking a Skywatcher’s ascension into greater wisdom and deeper communion with the celestial wilds.
The Skywatchers are a peaceful but deeply philosophical people, and their greatest conflicts often arise not from external threats but from within their own ranks. These disputes are rarely settled through violence, instead taking the form of long debates, quiet defiance, or rare moments of decisive action by the Elders.
Fate vs. Free Will – The most fundamental divide among the Skywatchers is whether the stars dictate fate absolutely or if mortals can alter destiny. The Constellarium Elders, including Sylwen Starbloom, generally believe the stars reveal an inevitable path, though it is up to mortals to follow it wisely.
More independent thinkers, like Therion Sylren before his passing, saw destiny as fluid, a story yet to be written rather than a rigid script. Isolation vs. Engagement Some Skywatchers believe the tribe should remain apart from the world, safeguarding their wisdom until the stars call upon them.
Others, particularly younger members, argue that the world is changing and that the Skywatchers must take a more active role in shaping the future. The Celestial Moot – When a matter of great importance divides the tribe, a gathering is held under the open sky. Each side presents its case, and the Elders cast their judgment after observing the stars for guidance.
Silent Defiance – Some younger Skywatchers, unwilling to openly challenge their Elders, instead quietly follow their own path, trusting that time will vindicate them.
The Wanderer’s Choice – If a Skywatcher truly disagrees with the tribe’s direction, they may invoke an old tradition: to leave and seek their own destiny, returning only when they have found proof that the stars themselves favor their path.
Long ago, when the Skywatchers were at the height of their celestial wisdom, the Star of Vaelis—a brilliant, sapphire-colored celestial body said to be the spirit of a great druid who ascended to the heavens—vanished from the night sky. For centuries, this star had been a guiding light for the Skywatchers, an omen of balance and wisdom, and a cornerstone of their prophecies.Its disappearance sent a ripple of fear through the tribe. If the stars were the ultimate guides of fate, how could one simply vanish? Had they misread the heavens? Had something undone a celestial truth?The event caused the greatest schism in the Skywatchers’ history, dividing them into three factions:
The Fatalists – These Elders insisted that the star’s disappearance was itself part of destiny, a sign of a great change that had already been set in motion. They argued that the Skywatchers should remain patient and watch the skies for further omens. Sylwen Starbloom, though young at the time, was a firm believer in this view, trusting that the stars never lied.
The Questioners – Some, including a few rebellious druids and hunters, believed the event proved that fate was not as absolute as the Elders had always taught. If a star—something eternal and untouchable—could disappear, then could the future truly be fixed? This group, which included Therion Sylren, began to question whether the Skywatchers were too rigid in their beliefs.
The Seekers – A small but radical sect believed that the star had not simply vanished, but had fallen, somewhere upon the Material Plane. They argued that their purpose was to find it—to seek proof that celestial fate could be altered. A few of them left the High Forest entirely, never to return.
For decades, the Skywatchers were in a state of quiet unrest. Some stopped reading the stars altogether, fearful that their interpretations had been wrong all along. Others doubled down on prophecy, searching endlessly for an explanation. The Seekers were officially exiled, and their names were no longer spoken in ritual.
But then, a new star appeared.
It was smaller, fainter, but in nearly the same position as the lost Star of Vaelis. Some said it was the original star, returned after an unknown celestial trial. Others believed it was a different star entirely, proof that even the heavens could change.Though the tribe ultimately reconciled, the divide left its mark. To this day, Skywatchers hold quiet debates over the meaning of the event. Some still whisper of the lost Seekers, wondering if they ever found what they were looking for. Others, like Sylwen, see it as a lesson in patience and faith. And those who take after Therion hold onto a quiet thought:
If even the stars can change, perhaps so can fate.The Skywatchers are divided into several sects, each with its own role in interpreting and protecting the wisdom of the heavens:
The Constellarium – The eldest scholars and diviners who study celestial patterns, seeking omens that shape the future.
The Mantle Wardens – Druids and rangers who embody the wild aspects of the Skyborn Mantle, wielding their shapeshifting abilities to protect sacred sites and maintain balance in the forest.
The Starborne Walkers – Wanderers who venture beyond the High Forest, seeking forgotten knowledge and lost celestial relics. Some never return, becoming legends whispered among their kin.
The Astral Scribes – Keepers of the oral and written histories, preserving ancient myths of fallen stars, celestial beings, and the first Skywatchers. Elarion the Stargazer – The first great scholar of the Skywatchers, said to have mapped the heavens long before written records existed. His observations were carved into silverwood tablets, many of which are still consulted by the Constellarium today.
Vaelis Starborn – A legendary druid who, according to myth, ascended to the heavens after donning the Skyborn Mantle one final time. Some claim he became the brightest star in the sky, while others believe he simply disappeared, proving that no fate is absolute.
The Shrouded Prophet – A nameless figure from an age long past, who once emerged from the depths of the High Forest to warn of a coming calamity. The prophecy was lost to time, but some elders whisper that the signs are returning. Sylwen Starbloom (Living Elder of the Skywatchers)
As one of the current Elders, Sylwen holds an esteemed position within the Constellarium, revered for her celestial readings and wisdom. Though she remains a staunch believer in destiny and the sacred duties of the Skywatchers, her vision for the future is one of measured caution. She has played a role in keeping the tribe isolated from outside influences, fearing that the world beyond will corrupt the purity of their traditions.
Therion Sylren (Beloved Hunter and Storyteller, Deceased)
Unlike many of his kin, Therion never saw the stars as rigid fate, but as stories waiting to be written. As a hunter and guide, he acted as a bridge between the tribe’s traditions and the desire for individual freedom. His tales inspired many young Skywatchers to question the strict teachings of the elders, making him both beloved and controversial. His death left a profound mark on the tribe, with some claiming it was an ill omen, while others saw it as proof that even the brightest stars must eventually fade.
"When the stars call, the sky answers, and so too must we."Among the Skywatchers of the High Forest, it is believed that every soul is woven from stardust, their fates whispered by the constellations. Those born under falling stars, like Kaelion, are seen as children of the sky—beings whose spirits are not bound to a single form. Instead, they are blessed with the Mantle of the Skyborn, the ability to shift their essence as freely as the wandering stars.
The term Skyborn Mantle comes from an ancient Skywatcher legend:
Long ago, the first of their kind stood atop the highest peaks, watching the sky for omens. One night, the heavens split open, and from the breach fell a being of pure light, its form shifting like mist under moonlight. It whispered to the watchers that all creatures, great and small, carry the spirit of the stars within them. To honor this truth, the Skywatchers learned to don the "mantle" of the beasts, walking the land as kin to the wilds and sky alike.
To "take on the Skyborn Mantle" is to embrace this sacred gift—the ability to transform, to bridge the celestial and the earthly, and to walk in harmony with the ever-changing dance of the cosmos.]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/locations/forgotten-realms/high-forest/the-skywatchers-of-the-high-forest.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Forgotten Realms/High Forest/The Skywatchers of the High Forest.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Olostin's Hold]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tavern:
<a data-href="The Flaming Skull" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/locations/forgotten-realms/olostin's-hold/the-flaming-skull-tavern/the-flaming-skull.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Flaming Skull</a>
Governant:
<br><a data-href="The Lady of the Hold" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/npc's/the-lady-of-the-hold.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Lady of the Hold</a>
]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/locations/forgotten-realms/olostin&apos;s-hold/olostin&apos;s-hold.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Forgotten Realms/Olostin&apos;s Hold/Olostin&apos;s Hold.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Eluna Stormwhisper]]></title><description><![CDATA[Race: Wood Elf
Class: Druid
Role: Apprentice Seeker, Aspiring Starwatcher, Close Friend to KaelionEluna was born into the Skywatcher Tribe, a group of wood elves who revered the stars and the natural world, believing that the heavens held important lessons and guidance. From a young age, Eluna was drawn to the night sky—an endless expanse full of mysteries waiting to be unlocked. However, unlike some of her peers, who seemed to understand the stars and their meanings instinctively, Eluna had to work hard to understand their language.She wasn’t born with the innate celestial connection many members of her tribe seemed to possess, and at first, she felt somewhat alienated from the other children who shared a natural understanding of the stars’ patterns and movements. Still, Eluna wasn’t the type to back down from a challenge. She spent hours on end, both during the day and at night, studying the stars, asking the tribe’s elders questions, and practicing rituals in hopes of finding a deeper connection to the celestial forces. The process was slow, and while she did begin to make sense of the constellations, she was still a long way from truly understanding the mysteries of the stars.Despite her struggles, Eluna’s determination to learn was undeniable. She wasn’t an instant prodigy, but through sheer persistence and patience, she became a solid part of the younger generation of Skywatchers. While she didn’t hold any official role or title, she was known within the tribe as someone who always asked the right questions—someone who was dedicated to learning even if she hadn’t quite unlocked the secrets the stars held. Eluna was still an apprentice when she left the tribe, focused on the quest for understanding, but not yet an influential figure within the Skywatcher Tribe.Kaelion and Eluna’s bond was formed over their shared interest in the stars. While Kaelion always had a natural connection to the world around them, Eluna’s interest was born of curiosity and a desire to find meaning. Kaelion admired Eluna’s tenacity, seeing in her a reflection of their own dedication to understanding the world in a way that felt deeply personal.Though they didn’t always agree on the best path forward, their relationship was one of mutual respect and camaraderie. They often spent nights together under the stars, discussing the movements of celestial bodies and wondering about the great mysteries of the universe. Kaelion sometimes found Eluna's fascination with understanding everything to be a bit obsessive, but they respected her search for meaning and the questions she wasn’t afraid to ask, no matter how uncomfortable. In turn, Eluna appreciated Kaelion’s more intuitive approach to the world, admiring the way they found balance without always needing to question or rationalize everything.]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/npc&apos;s/eluna-stormwhisper.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/NPC&apos;s/Eluna Stormwhisper.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Lady of the Hold]]></title><description><![CDATA[Name: Tamalin
Location: <a data-href="Olostin's Hold" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/locations/forgotten-realms/olostin's-hold/olostin's-hold.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Olostin's Hold</a>Quests:
<br>Have the <a data-href="Party" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/party.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Party</a> investigate and deal with the werewolf/shapeshift issues around <a data-href="Olostin's Hold" href="https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/locations/forgotten-realms/olostin's-hold/olostin's-hold.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Olostin's Hold</a>. ]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/npc&apos;s/the-lady-of-the-hold.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/NPC&apos;s/The Lady of the Hold.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Arnihl]]></title><description><![CDATA[Arnihl is portrayed by JovanA 2.2m tall Goliath with gray skin, no hair and completely black eyes drinking his problems away - hails from the Spine of the world]]></description><link>https://TheOnlyKay.github.io/characters/playable-characters/arnihl/arnihl.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Playable Characters/Arnihl/Arnihl.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOnlyKay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>